// WRITE OUT QUIZ OBJECT HERE FIRST
// THEN USE ONLINE SERVICE TO TRANSFORM INTO JSON FILE

const quiz = {
  "1": {
    question: "What is JavaScript?",
    1: "A computer programming language",
    2: "An alien language",
    3: "Another name for Java",
    4: "A robot name",
    answer: 1,
  },
  "2": {
    question:
      "What is the built-in array method used to remove an element at index 0",
    1: "splice(0,1)",
    2: "pop()",
    3: "shift()",
    4: "push()",
    answer: 3,
  },
  "3": {
    question:
      "What is printed in the console after the following code runs? const flowers = [ 'rose', 'lily', 'peony', 'jasmine']; console.log(flowers.pop()); ",
    1: "[ 'rose', 'lily', 'peony', 'jasmine']",
    2: "jasmine",
    3: "3",
    4: "rose",
    answer: 2,
  },
  "4": {
    question:
      "What is printed in the console after the following code runs? console.log(false === 'false')",
    1: "false",
    2: "'false'",
    3: "1",
    4: "true",
    answer: 1,
  },
  "5": {
    question:
      "What is printed in the console after the following code runs? console.log(true + false / true + true)",
    1: "1",
    2: "NaN",
    3: "0",
    4: "2",
    answer: 4,
  },
  "6": {
    question:
      "What is the correct JavaScript syntax to change the content of this HTML tag? <div id='quiz'>Hello, World!</div>",
    1: "document.getElement('div').innerHTML = 'Heyyy, Earth!'",
    2: "document.getElementById('div').innerHTML = 'Heyyy, Earth!'",
    3: "#quiz.innerHTML = 'Heyyy, Earth!'",
    4: "document.getElementById('quiz').innerHTML = 'Heyyy, Earth!'",
    answer: 4,
  },
  "7": {
    question: "How do you write a comment in JavaScript?",
    1: "{/* this is a JS comment */}",
    2: "// this is a JS comment",
    3: "<!-- this is a JS comment -->",
    4: "/ this is a JS comment */",
    answer: 2,
  },
  "8": {
    question: "How do you round the number 3.50 to the nearest integer?",
    1: "math.round(3.50)",
    2: "Math.round(3.50)",
    3: "Math.down(3.50)",
    4: "Math.rnd(3.50)",
    answer: 2,
  },
  "9": {
    question: "How do you declare a variable in JavaScipt?",
    1: "string greatestBaseballTeam = 'Anaheim Angels'",
    2: "var greatestBaseballTeam: 'Anaheim Angels'",
    3: "let greatestBaseballTeam = 'Anaheim Angels'",
    4: "greatestBaseballTeam = 'Anaheim Angels'",
    answer: 3,
  },
  "10": {
    question: "Choose the object.",
    1: "'object'",
    2: "08Jec7",
    3: "[ 5, 6, 7, 8 ]",
    4: "true",
    answer: 3,
  },
  "11": {
    question: "What is this? () => {}",
    1: "A pure function",
    2: "An anonymous function",
    3: "An arrow function",
    4: "A Java function",
    answer: 3,
  },
  "12": {
    question: "What year was JavaScript introduced?",
    1: "1992",
    2: "1993",
    3: "1994",
    4: "1995",
    answer: 4,
  },
  "13": {
    question: "Which browser was JavaScript developed for?",
    1: "Netscape Navigator",
    2: "Safari",
    3: "Internet Explorer",
    4: "Mosaic",
    answer: 1,
  },
};
